<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Givings on Xi Chapter Alumni Association</title>
    <link>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Givings on Xi Chapter Alumni Association</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.alumxi.com/giving/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Capital Campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/capital/</guid>
      <description>We are announcing our first 22nd annual capital campaign.  $1,222,222    10% Funded  $126,254  Raised    Click here to set up a donation!   253 Commonwealth Ave is the hub of the hub of the universe. Living at the house was the foundation around which our MIT experience was built, and having lived there is still a large part of our lives. As we know, college friendships last a very long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate to Alumxi</title>
      <link>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/alumxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/alumxi/</guid>
      <description>AlumXi needs your help! We are here to make sure that Tep endures, helping future Teply MIT students find a place they can make their own, just as we all did. To do that, we need your financial support.
Note that AlumXi is a 501(c)7 not-for-profit and contributions are not tax-deductible. If that is a significant concern, you can donate to certain MIT funds instead.
How much to give? If at all possible, we encourage setting up a recurring, monthly donation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving to MIT</title>
      <link>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/mit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/mit/</guid>
      <description>Giving money to MIT helps maintain MIT’s educational excellence and assists the current generation of MIT students to cope with eye-popping cost of an MIT education.
There are two funds of particular interest to MIT alumni of TEP:
The FredFund Fred Fenning was a beloved member of TEP who died after his airplane experienced a mechanical failure. Fred donated his time generously to the house after graduating and his technical abilities and warm-hearted nature were an inspiration to generations of TEPs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>