<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Givings on Xi Chapter Alumni Association</title>
    <link>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Givings on Xi Chapter Alumni Association</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.alumxi.com/giving/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2022 Capital Campaign</title>
      <link>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/capital/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/capital/</guid>
      <description>We are announcing our first 22nd annual capital campaign. Donate 253 Commonwealth Ave is the hub of the hub of the universe. Whom among us does not recall the house and all that it meant and still means to us? Living at the house was the foundation around which our MIT experience was built, and having lived there is still a large part of our lives. As we know, college friendships last a very long time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate to Alumxi</title>
      <link>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/alumxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/alumxi/</guid>
      <description>Note that AlumXi is a 501(c)7 not-for-profit and contributions are not tax-deductible. If that is a significant concern, you can donate to certain MIT funds instead.
How to Make a One-Time Donation via PayPal You can make a donation via PayPal using the “Donate” button below. You get to pick the amount of your donation. May we suggest $22.22 or $222.22?
 Monthly Donations via PayPal You can also make a make a recurring monthly donation via PayPal using the “Subscribe” button below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving to MIT</title>
      <link>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/mit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.alumxi.com/giving/mit/</guid>
      <description>Giving money to MIT helps maintain MIT’s educational excellence and assists the current generation of MIT students to cope with eye-popping cost of an MIT education.
There are two funds of particular interest to MIT alumni of TEP:
The FredFund Fred Fenning was a beloved member of TEP who died after his airplane experienced a mechanical failure. Fred donated his time generously to the house after graduating and his technical abilities and warm-hearted nature were an inspiration to generations of TEPs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>