<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>About on Xi Chapter Alumni Association</title>
    <link>https://ggilmore.github.io/tep-alumni-website/</link>
    <description>Recent content in About on Xi Chapter Alumni Association</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ggilmore.github.io/tep-alumni-website/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ggilmore.github.io/tep-alumni-website/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ggilmore.github.io/tep-alumni-website/about/</guid>
      <description>The Alumni Association of Xi Chapter of Tau Epsilon Phi, Inc., or AlumXi, aim to promote fellowship and communication amongst current members and Alumni of of the Xi Chapter of Tau Epsilon Phi, to promote fellowship and communication between Xi and other Tau Epsilon Phi chapters, and to promote fellowship and communication between Xi and TEP National. We also aim to engage in activities that improve relations between Xi Chapter and the community, engage in activities that help provide safe and affordable housing for students, and to provide for scholastic, educational and managerial opportunities for the chapter and its members.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donate to Alumxi</title>
      <link>https://ggilmore.github.io/tep-alumni-website/giving/alumxi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ggilmore.github.io/tep-alumni-website/giving/alumxi/</guid>
      <description>Annual dues for the Alumni Association of Xi Chapter of Tau Epsilon Phi Inc are $5. Any amount above $5 will be considered a donation. Note that AlumXi is a 501(c)7 not-for-profit and contributions are not tax-deductible.
How to Make a Donation via PayPal You can make a donation via PayPal using the “Donate” button below. You get to pick the amount of your donation.
 How to Make a Monthly Donation via PayPal You can make a make a recurring monthly donation via PayPal using the “Subscribe” button below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Form 990s</title>
      <link>https://ggilmore.github.io/tep-alumni-website/taxes/form-990/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ggilmore.github.io/tep-alumni-website/taxes/form-990/</guid>
      <description>According to IRS regulations not-for-profit organizations must make their tax records available for public inspection.
🚨 NOTE: These links are inactive. The PDFs shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be stored in git. We need to find a stable storage solution.
Organizational documents and public filings of Alumni Association of Xi Chapter of Tau Epsilon Phi, Inc.  Articles of Organization 2009 Form 990EZ 2010 Form 990EZ 2011 Form 990EZ 2012 Form 990EZ  Organizational documents and public filings of MIT Alumni of TEP Student Aid Foundation, Inc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giving to MIT</title>
      <link>https://ggilmore.github.io/tep-alumni-website/giving/mit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ggilmore.github.io/tep-alumni-website/giving/mit/</guid>
      <description>Giving money to MIT helps maintain MIT’s educational excellence and assists the current generation of MIT students to cope with eye-popping cost of an MIT education.
There are two funds of particular interest to MIT alumni of TEP:
The FredFund Fred Fenning was a beloved member of TEP who died after his airplane experienced a mechanical failure. Fred donated his time generously to the house after graduating and his technical abilities and warm-hearted nature were an inspiration to generations of TEPs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>